sharewareguide.net 2005-12-12

# www.sharewareguide.net - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Sharewareguide.net and please read it in full. Sharewareguide.net understands the importance of security and privacy, so always thinks it our responsibility to respect and protect the privacy of every user and ensure the integrity of internet by using every reasonable means. Please give us abundant confidence about the ability to ensure your confidentiality and to maintain your trust.

The privacy policy is detailed as follows:

Sharewareguide.net does not utilize cookies on this site. However, some of our partners sites may use cookies and therefore you should review their privacy policies.

Sharewareguide.net guarantees that the software that you download from our site doesn't include the spyware and advertisement.

We collect no personally-identifiable information about you when you visit our website. The majority of our services don't require any form of user registration except for the special explain. 

The email address that you send to us to utilize requesting help will only be used to send replies to you. We don't reveal your email address to third parties.

Email address is required for participation in our Newsletters. Sharewareguide.net will send Newsletters only to customers who request the Newsletter, and will provide these customers with a simple and easy method to unsubscribe at their desire. At no time will Sharewareguide.net provide your personal information to third parties.

If you purchase product from Sharewareguide.net, additional information is needed to fill your order. But please note that the purchase transaction is directly carried out on the platform provided by Regnow. So Sharewareguide.net does not have access to any of customer information that you provide to Regnow. Any and all information collected through Regnow system is treated with its utmost care. For detailed information about this, please refer to the [privacy policy of Regnow](http://www.regnow.com/privacy.html).

**Note**

Using these Services signifies your agreement to this Privacy Policy, and please do not use the Services if you don't agree to it.

All the links provided in Sharewareguide.net are third parties links and all other trademarks are sole property of their respective owners. We have no relationship with any of the authors or companies. It is a pity that we are not responsible for any dissension owing to this. 

Sharewareguide.net promises to protect the confidentiality of users. If for any concern about our products and website's privacy policy, please address your question in an email to:[ **support@sharewareguide.net**](mailto:%20support@sharewareguide.net). All questions will be responded to within 2 business days.
